The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
I'm here.
What's on your mind ?
A grade 6 pill is unheard of in a rank 3 country,
not to mention a Return to Origin pill.
I'm afraid even Senior Ouyang Zi
won't be able to make it.
Wan'er,
in the whole Cloud Sky Sect,
the person that is most likely to reach Soul Formation
is Ouyang Zi.
He's obsessed with the Dao of alchemy.
That obsession to understand the heavens
will lead him to Soul Formation in the future...
I'm sure of it.
Don't worry,
Ouyang Zi will definitely make the pill.
Wrong...
Wrong !
It's wrong...
Even that is wrong...
Ancestor.
It's wrong !
It's all wrong !
Peak grade 5...
That's not enough.
If it takes too long to make the pill,
Wan'er's body might not hold on for long enough.
Don't disturb me
unless it's absolutely necessary.
Is it this one ?
If you need anything else,
Or this one ?
you know where to find me.
It's wrong !
Wan'er is reaching the end of her lifespan.
She's been relying on pills for years
so reaching Nascent Soul is the only way.
But it's against the law of the heavens...
It's incompatible...
The law of the heavens
is not invisible.
It exists somewhere between heaven and earth
and interferes with our world.
Dragon restriction !
When Wan'er reaches Nascent Soul,
if it really comes for her with a tribulation,
this restriction will hold it back.
3 years later
With the Ancestor's restrictions,
this valley has become the most impregnable place in Chu.
But what is the Ancestor guarding us against ?
Senior,
You said that the Celestial Realm was shattered countless years ago
but that it's still magnificent.
Can I see it ?
Don't wait for the future love,
We'll travel on the star compass
so you can see mountains, rivers, pavilions and palaces
of the Celestial Realm.
the soul between your eyebrows is already peaceful.
Maybe
there are still remnants of Celestial Beasts to be found.
Senior,
Ask the palm lines of time...
I'd like to go to the Four Sect Alliance
to see the mortal's capital
and also
Sincerely entrust your love, don't waste time.
that old street you lived in.
Sure.
I promised in my dreams
that from now on no one will block our path.
In the blink of an eye, I will change the world.
These nights of longing in the past...
Wan'er
When you're better,
Deep in my heart,
come back to Zhao with me,
I believed that you and I
to the Wang Family Village.
can cross the line between life and death.
What do you think ?
We will overcome our doomed fate.
The night won't last forever.
Do you believe in
the unbreakable reincarnation cycle ?
After seeing your beautiful face
on our first meeting.
I believe
fate cannot destroy our vows.
The law of the heavens is unpredictable.
I don't know if it can manifest in other ways than a tribulation.
Wan'er !
The Life and Death Domain can no longer suppress the death aura !
A Grade 6 pill !
I, Ouyang Zi, completed it !
The Return to Origin pill is extremely potent,
enough for it to be harmful to her body.
It should be able suppress the death aura enough
for it to be expelled.
When Wan'er reaches Nascent Soul,
I will use the strength of the Life and Death Domain,
plus the power of the pagoda.
I'm sure it will give her enough time to form her Nascent Soul.
It's working.
Condense !
It's coming...
This tribulation is really strong.
Li Muwan's
Nascent Soul
Break !
These dozens of restrictions I placed over the past 3 years
were barely able to block a single attack from the tribulation...
The power of the law of the heavens
is terrifying.
I did it !
This is...
the death aura ?!
Impossible...
Wan'er reached Nascent Soul.
Her lifespan should've extended.
Why is there so much death aura ?
The law of the heavens...
came in person...
Hand of the law of the heavens
Wan'er !
Senior...
I'm willing to give up everything.
Even if all my past lives are destroyed.
But this is
the karma between us.
This is the choice of the heavens.
We...
After all, we are like ink and water
struggling under the heavens.
Senior,
even if time goes by,
the law of the heavens won't allow
Wan'er to live.
Since you're here...
No...
I have no regrets...
NOOOO !!!
Wan'er !
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
So what if it's the law of the heavens ?
the law of the heavens ?
I will fight back !
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
Even if the heavens want you to die,
within my warm fingers ?
I will steal you back !
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
Original body !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
Wan'er's body dissipated
the shackles of our fate.
but her Nascent Soul has been formed.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.
Senior !
What can be done against the law of the heavens ?
It dares to use a tribulation against your body
to make you enter the cycle of reincarnation.
I cultivate to break free from worldly delusions.
If you want to exercise the law of the heavens
you will have to kill me first !
I only understand when I'm regretful.
What's the point of not letting go ?
I wish I could turn around and just look away
from your eyes.
Fist of the law of the heavens
But they're worth it.
Apricot Village
I'm the only one that can see
this battle with law of the heavens.
Wan'er...
Look !
What's that ?
What's wrong with the Sun today ?
Oh my God,
the Moon is out too !
What's going on ?
What's happening ?
The Sun and Moon are shining together ?
Wang Lin
merged bodies
Soul Formation
and 2-stars Ancient God
You want to destroy Wan'er's Nascent Soul
and erase her existence.
I, Wang Lin, won't let you !
I did it !
Now,
she has been reincarnated with her Nascent Soul
so her lifespan has been extended.
This falls in line with the law of the heavens.
19 years from now
when her Nascent Soul reforms,
I know you will come back !
But next time,
I will stop you again !
Is this the punishment for defying the heavens ?
I will cultivate the Life and Death reincarnation cycle.
And one day,
I will take your place !
At that time,
I will remake the law of the heavens
to do as I, Wang Lin, wish.
I will make you
kneel before me !
Here's an emotional passage of the novel that couldn't be fully adapted:
Li Muwan’s eyes showed a deep sense of reluctance. She looked at Wang Lin with a nostalgic gaze and then looked around before slowly closing her eyes. A teardrop fell from the corner of her eye.
The teardrop slowly fell down, creating a weak sound when it landed on the ground.
This sound entered Wang Lin’s ears. It made him feel like the past was collapsing…
No one knew if where that tear fell will create a field of memories and sorrow by next year…
The moment she closed her eyes, her Golden Core immediately dimmed and then shattered soon after. A small person who looked exactly like the Li Muwan of the past appeared. Her eyes were pure, but they quickly closed due to Li Muwan’s death.
Wang Lin, I’m willing to give up everything. Even if the stars fall, as long as you are willing to accompany me, your heart is the brightest light.
Wang Lin, I’m willing to give up everything. Even if all my past lives are destroyed, it won’t extinguish my reluctance to leave you.
Wang Lin, I’m willing to give up everything. Even if my life ends, even if time passes on, I hope the flower of memories never wilts.
Wang Lin, this is the karma between us. This is the choice of the heavens. After all, we are like ink and water struggling under the heavens.
Falling from the night sky and melting into dust
like water without a source.
Like the difference between clouds and mud,
the truth cannot be found in conflict.
Life and death
are like the moment when the rain falls
and like many other unseparable things.
In this lifetime,
to cultivate the truth, cultivate the world first.
Old grudges had to be settled
because half an inch is engraved into my tree rings.
Use the most vivid love and hate
to ask questions to your fate.
Let your eyes be filled enough with rage
to pierce the heart and the soul
then soften because of the mortals' fireworks.
Only when you bend down can you understand
the hidden edge of the blade.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
The human mind is nature,
the rain fell silently like an answer.
Life and death are just moments away,
there are many other solutions to grudges.
Use your dusty heart
to depict the world.
One stroke is for killing.
After struggling for hundreds of years, I endured letting go.
One stroke is for caring.
Everywhere there is life, there are thousands of lights.
Give up your mind to be refined
by this endless world.
Snow falls as my hair turns white, winter withers
while prosperity sprouts in summer.
I step into the world, with light at my fingertips,
the law of cause and effect.
I observe the vastness of heaven and earth so I can get rid of evil.
Obsession arises from one thought, life and death arise from one thought.
Reincarnation is not to be feared.